Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory9 Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents M
  - McGee, W.J. (Box 59)
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1897 Jan. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1897 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Sept. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 3; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 July 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 July 21; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 12, Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Sept. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1901 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 3
    - To Boas, 1901 May 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 22
    - To Boas, 1901 Sept. 23
    - To Boas, 1901 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 19; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 19; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 June 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 July 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 July 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Oct. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 16; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 18; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 June 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1905 June 7
    - To Boas, 1905 July 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 May 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 11; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 26
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 11; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 2, Mar. 19, Apr. 2; (7p)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 3 and 6
    - W.J. McGee -- to Dr. Daniel Brinton, 1898 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to W.H. Holmes, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to H.H. St. Clair, 1901 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to Charles D. Walcott, 1910 Jan. 26; 7p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to Charles D. Walcott, 1910 Apr. 20; 3p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to Charles D. Walcott, 1910 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - W.J. McGee -- to R.S. Woodward, 1905 Mar. 20
  - McGhee, Paul A. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - See Hook, Sidney, Jan. 2, 1934.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 27; 1p.
      (Enc: Bursar's report.)
  - McGiffert, A.C. (Box 59)
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 1p.
  - McGill University (Box 59)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 3; teleg.
      see also Brittain, W.H.
  - McGin (Box 59)
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 19
  - McGoldrick, J. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p.
  - McGregor, J.H. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 23; 1p.
  - McGregor Fund (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
  - McGuff, Peter (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July; receipt
  - McGuire, James W. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - J.W. McGuire -- to James McCormick, 1926 Feb. 24; 2p.
  - McGuire, Joseph D. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 7
  - McHugh, G.M. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 23; 1p.
  - McHugh, J.M. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 1p.
  - Mach, E. von (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1919 July 29; 3p.
  - Machacek, Gerald (Box 60)
    - See Mead, Nelson P., Nov. 15, 1939.
  - McIlwraith, T.F. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 21; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Fleming, D.I. July 25, 1927., 1932 Jan. 15; 2p.
  - MacInnes, T.R.L. (Box 60)
    - To R.F. Benedict, 1938 Aug. 11; 1p.
  - McIntire, C. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 11
  - MacIver, R.M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Dunn, L.C., June 8, 1934)
    - From Boas, 1934 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Hayden, P.M. to MacIver, R.M. Apr. 15, 1931., 1931 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc: Ross, F.A. to Sub-Committee of anthropology and social science), 1934 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - R.M. MacIver -- from P.M. Hayden, 1931 Apr. 15
    - (Enc. with MacIver, R.M. Apr. 17, 1931, 1941 Apr. 18
  - Mack, J.W. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 24; 1p.
  - Mackall, Lawton (Box 60)
    - See Boas, F. to Lombardo, Carmyn J., Oct. 14, 1940.
  - MacKay, D.M. (Box 60)
    - D.M. MacKay -- from R.F. Benedict, 1938 Aug. 19
    - D.M. MacKay -- to R.F. Benedict, 1938 Aug. 26; 1p.
  - McKay, Mrs. Joshua C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept. 12; 1p.
  - Mackay, J.W. (Box 60)
    - J.W. Mackay -- to J.A. Tait, 1895 June 11; postcard
  - Mackaye, Ruth (Mrs. W.V.) (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 24; 2p.
  - Mackaye, W.V. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 30; 1p.
      (Enc: Thesis outline)
  - McKee, Frances (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - F. McKee -- from Roger Baldwin, 1941 Mar. 6
  - McKee, W.J. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 6
    - To Boas, 1910 May 25
  - McKelvie, B.A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 6; 3p.
  - McKenney, Ruth (Box 60)
    - See Brooks, V.W., Nov. 22, 1938.
  - Mackenzie, Dudley S. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 25; 1p.
  - McKern, W.C. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1926 June 29; 2p.
  - Mackie, Ransom A. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 28; 1p.
  - MacKinlay, W.E.W. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov.?; 1p.
  - McKnight, N.M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 16; 1p.
  - McKnight, R.G. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 3p.
  - Mackowey? (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 13
  - Maclanni, Richarde (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec.; 1p.
  - Maclaurin, R.C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 12
  - McLean, A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
  - McLean, John (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1889 June 5
  - MacLean, M.S. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 2; 1p.
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 4; 1p.
  - MacLeod, W.C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - McLoughlin, Mary M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p.
  - McLouth, Lawrence A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - See Margin: Boas, F. to McLouth, A. Mar. 11, 1905., 1906 Mar. 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 11; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 30; 2p.
  - McMahon, A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; 1p.
  - McMahon, Mrs. Philip (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
  - Macmillan, Kerr D. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 18; 1p.
  - MacMillan, Mrs. Wade (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 4p.
  - Macmillan Co. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1919 July 28
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 30; bill
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; bill
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 29; account
    - To Boas, 1930 June 26; 1p.
    - (Enc: Macmillan to A.S. Waldstein June 26, 1930, 1930 July 30; statement
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 29
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 29
    - To Boas, 1939 July; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 29
    - Macmillan Co. -- from J.F. Jameson, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - Macmillan Co. -- to A.S. Waldstein, 1930 June 26; 1p.
    - See: Latham, H.F.
    - Cole, Lois Dwight, (4-1-36, 4-2-36, 7-7-36, 3-31-34)
    - McCurdy, Henry B., 4-8-36
    - Morehouse, T.C., 7-3-36, 7-6-36, 12-23-36, 12-28,1936)
    - Putnam, A.J., 1-4-33, 1-5-33
    - Hale, Everett, 1-31-33
  - MacMillan, D.P. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9
    - To Boas, 1908 June 5
  - McMillin, Emerson (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 11
    - E.McMillin -- to E.O. Hovey, 1913 Nov. 10
  - McMurrict, J.P. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 14
  - McMurtrie, D.C. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1917 May 2
    - From Boas, 1917 May 11
    - From Boas, 1917 June 11
    - From Boas, 1917 June 12
    - To Boas, 1916 July 18
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 May 3
  - McNary, Martha (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - McNicoll, Robert E. (Box 60)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - McNutt, Waldo R. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 13; 2p.
  - McQuown, Norman A. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 3; 1p.
  - Macrae, J.A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 21
  - McVey, Frank L. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1897 May 15; 1p.
  - McWhood?, L.B. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Madelgroot, J.J. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
  - Madieros, John Matthew (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1930 May 8; 1p.
  - Maerker-Branden, A.P. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 2; 1p.
  - Maes, D. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1926; 3p.
  - Magie, D. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 2
    - D. Magie -- to Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 22
  - Magnus, Max (Box 60)
    - See Anon., 1920 Dec. 31
  - Magoon, Charles E. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1903 Apr. 25; 1p.
  - Mahalanobis, P.C. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Eickstedt, O.M. von, Feb. 21, 1928)
  - Maher, J.J. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 23; 1p.
  - Mahr?, A. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1923 July 18; 4p.
  - Majumdar, D.N. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 27; 1p.
  - Malaga (Box 60)
    - To the intellectuals of America who signed the petition to General Franco..., 1937 Dec.; 4p.
  - Malán, M.N. (Box 60)
    - See Boas, F. to Wright, E.H., Mar. 16, 1931.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 25; 1p.
  - Malcolm, Alexander (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Malcom, M.V. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally in Malcom, M.V. Apr. 8, 1925, 1925 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letter of introduction - Apr. 7, 1925, 1925 Apr.?; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Boas, F., Apr. 27, 1925)
  - Malecot, G.L. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - Malécot, Violette (Mrs. J.L.) (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 4; 3p.
  - Malinowski, Bronislaw (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Boas, F. to Bush, W.T., Oct. 13, 1928)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: Malinowski, B. to Warner, L. May 5, 1933, 1933 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - B. Malinowski -- to L. Warner, 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Malinowski, B., May 5, 1933)
  - Malisoff, W.M. (Box 60)
    - From Boas
      - See Boas, F. to Dearborn, N.H., Dec. 17, 1940.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 21; 2p.
      (Enc: Educational Council of University)
  - Mall, F.P. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
  - Mallery, Garrick (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1887 June 7
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 15
  - Mallory, M.A. (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 30; 1p.
  - Malkau? (Box 60)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 19; 1p.
  - Malnutrition Plan Study (Box 60)
    See Rivers, W.H.R.
  - Maly, J. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 25; 2p.
  - Malzberg, Benjamin (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from Frederick W. Parsons to Karpf, Maurice J. Jan. 29, 1935, 1935 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from Truesdell, Leon E. to Malzberg, Benjamin Feb. 15, 1935, 1935 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from Austin, W.L. to Malzberg, B. Mar. 4, 1935, 1935 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 13; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 1p.
    - B. Malzberg -- from W.L. Austin, 1935 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - B. Malzberg -- from Bruno Klopfer, 1936 June 22; 1p.
    - B. Malzberg -- from Bruno Klopfer, 1936 Oct. 19
    - B. Malzberg -- from Bruno Klopfer, 1936 Nov. 10
    - B. Malzberg -- to Bruno Klopfer, 1936 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - B. Malzberg -- from Leon E. Truesdell, 1935 Feb. 15; 1p.
  - Manabozho, Chief (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec.; 2p.
  - Manach, Jorge (Box 60)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
  - Mandel, John A. (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec.; 1p.
  - Mandelbaum, May (Mrs. Edel) (Box 60)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 11; 2p.